pr-club.net 2009-02-15

# iEntry Network - Privacy Policy

iEntry reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying users through a notice posted on iEntry.com or by email, of the existence of a new privacy policy or any updates. 

**Registration**  
iEntry respects and is committed to protecting your privacy. That is why this Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and explains data collection and use practices for iEntry Inc. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to third parties. iEntry is the sole owner of the information collected on all our sites. 

iEntry collects personally identifying information during the registration process. Information is collected in certain portions of iEntry in which users specifically and knowingly provide such information along with content submissions, Directory submissions, membership sites or suggestions etc,. iEntry collects information from our users at several different points within our websites. iEntry may use such information for its internal purposes, including, but not limited to, editorial and feedback purposes. If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletters, alerts, updates, briefings etc. we ask for contact and delivery information like name and e-mail address. All of these e-mail lists provide opt out capabilities online and within each e-mail broadcast. On some of our sites the user is asked to provide optional demographic and personal interest information that is used to keep our content as fresh and relevant as possible. Information submitted at the time of registration (including newsletter subscriptions) may be used for marketing and promotional purposes by iEntry. If a guest objects to such use for any reason, he/she may stop that use by an e-mail request to [**support@ientry.com**](mailto:support@ientry.com). 

**Cookies**  
Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes while at the site. Cookies make Web-surfing easier by, among other things, saving your passwords and preferences for you. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and you'll find cookies at most major Web sites. 

Cookies help make iEntry better, by showing how and when guests use the site. Many content improvements and updates are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. A cookie lets iEntry remember that you've registered, which allows us to speed up your future activities at our sites. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifying information although it may enable iEntry to relate a user's use of iEntry to personally identifying information that has previously been submitted by the user, if any. 

You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers. These cookies are sent from third-party computers and are subject to such third parties' policies. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, it is likely that most areas of the site will not function properly if you do so. 

**Removal from our Database**  
Should you ever wish to be removed from our database, simply contact us and we will be happy to fulfill your request. Additionally, should you wish further clarification of this policy, please do not hesitate to email us at [**support@ientry.com**](mailtop:support@ientry.com).
